Let's do this.
Be right with you.
Hello?
Hey, fellas.
Hercules!
What happened in there?
I don't know. Get him inside.
Load up!
Where the hell's Einstein?
Fallen back.
Hey, this is Chloe. I'm heading right now, so leave a message and I'll get right back to you.
Hi, Chloe, it's Lo.
I'm officially out of the dorm and on my way back to the Kent.
But I realized I'm still getting my mail at your place.
Can you ring it by in the morning?
Okay. Thanks. Bye.
Oh, my God. What have I done?
Oh, my God.
Okay. I didn't see you, okay?
We're gonna get you out of here.
Okay.
You're gonna be fine.
I know you're gonna be fine.
Everyone I've ever hit was all right.
But...
No.
Come on.
I want to be there, too.
I know.
I don't know how you feel about pulling out two burning burning Confederate judges just for a point.
I know, but 2 are шт69DE.
GI
M prisм kilograms
M.
Jane
civil
for you
I made this whole world shine for you
Yeah, yeah, come on
Hey, I was just getting in. What are you guys doing?
Seem to have a visitor, a hungry visitor
Hey, he's supposed to be tied up in the barn
I chained him to a post for a second so that I could get my stuff out of the car and well...
Yeah
I had him chained right there
Okay, that's just bad wood
That's not my fault
How'd that post break?
Oh, my allergies suck
Where did you say you found him?
Actually, I kind of...
hit him
You hit him? With your car?
No, with my fist
I was gonna call the vet, but when I got in just now, he seemed fine
I think you need to go
You need to make some flyers in the morning
That way maybe we can figure out who he belongs to
He's got a collar, I'm sure somebody's missing him
Fine with me
Actually, it might be fun to have a dog around
Maybe if we can't find out who owns him, we could keep him
Why don't we just see what happens tomorrow, Clark?
Yeah, don't get too attached
I'm going to bed
Should I get some sleep?
You know, I'm gonna do my chores
It's three o'clock in the morning
Dad, since Lois is staying here, if I'm gonna do my work at super speed, I have to do it when she's not looking
All right, then why don't you start with that?
Come on
Sweetie, you should, at least, hang out around the shop
I know what you are talking about
I know what you're talking about
Listen, Scott, I'm the only one here
Maybe we should better fix you off
Your wife is thinking that, though
I guess I should have heard from theiragt
Was it because of me or did you know anything about him?
How this happened,
There's been a juicy conversation
about being Have a bunch of fuckars
in neighboring Belani
Hey, Chloe.
Hey.
Lois had her mail forwarded to my apartment.
Is she around?
Yeah, she's probably still in the shower.
Who's the puppy?
We don't know his name.
Lois found him.
She's bringing home strays now, huh?
Who is the new tenant?
Lois?
Well, she re-recorded her answering machine.
She uses all the hot water.
Oh, and she took over my bedroom.
She's doing great.
Okay.
How are you?
I don't know.
It's just kind of hard to be myself with her around.
Yeah, but now you got this guy.
You can be yourself around him, right?
And I'm always around.
We're coming back in two weeks.
It's
a success.
I'm hoping she'll be back soon enough,
so we can bring her stuff home.
We should walk her back together and walk her home.
You know, like, you know, if you're a destitute,
you feel like it.
You're not alone, right?
Maybe somebody needs you out here.
We're here and you're here to help.
Do you even have aen shores?
I'm sorry, this works.
Not really.
From $50K?
Stay.
Oh, boy.
Hey.
Looks like you got a secret, too.
Where you from?
You good boy.
What did you do?
What?
Oh, I, uh, must have rolled.
Through a fence?
Yeah, weird, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, weird.
But, I mean, it happens.
You know, the emergency brake must have slipped or something.
It's old, you know, it's an old tractor.
It is old.
Anyway, I'm gonna get going.
I'll see you guys around.
Bye.
Just playing with Skippy here.
We're not gonna call it a day.
I'm Skippy.
Okay, Lois, what would you like to call him?
Well, let's see.
He's annoying, and I can't seem to get within ten feet of him without getting sick.
I think we should call him Clarky.
Come here, Clarky.
Come here, boy.
Made up some flyers.
He can be somebody else's allergy now.
You know what, I don't think we're gonna have to use those.
I found one of those microchip ID tags under his skin.
I think they can scan at the animal shelter.
I spent all morning on these.
I'll be right back.
I have to tell my parents something.
Don't give me that look.
Clarky.
You should probably get your mom a new pot roast while we're out.
Sick, Clarky.
Good dog.
Crazy old Asian signiana is gone.
cant't be the same home.
angel, what happened to Freezel, RBFJ?
Four years later, Larry Hammer is walking away from his family.
If you want to get check out at any moment,
first thing you have to do is go to what is now the Hell loops.
The cause of death is what brings you halfway
to aцион dangers and çekiong procedures
before you can solve the cause of death.
Then, whoever fragrances that and runs the dog can
become the hub of protection or give you one of the clients.
Is it the E part you don't like?
Because we could always just make it Clark,
but then that would get really confusing.
And, hey, maybe you should consider changing your name.
You could be Skipper.
Anyway, uh, we think you might have an I.D. chip.
We were wondering if you could scan it for us.
If it's not too much trouble.
Um, well, sure, I guess.
Whoa. Easy boy.
Yeah, he doesn't seem to have a lot of love for you.
Maybe I should do that.
Bless you.
Thanks.
Luthorcourt.
You're kidding.
Huh.
Must be one of those lab dogs.
Lab dogs or something.
Lab dogs?
I'd be happy to take them off your hands and return them for you.
Actually, you know what?
That's okay. We'll take care of it.
Thanks.
It's okay.
Come on, buddy. Come on.
I should probably get your name and address, though.
In case someone from Luthorcourt calls.
It's policy.
Would you mind taking him back to the farm?
I'm gonna go talk to Lex.
Terrific.
Come on. Let's go sneeze a while.
He'll...
Clark, you're right.
Thanks.
Hey, Josh.
Guess who just showed up?
Einstein.
Yeah.
Some guy named Clark Kent's keeping him out on his farm.
That's good news, little brother.
Because I was thinking that we were gonna have to rob that truck tomorrow with just this dummy.
Why do you have to do that?
What do you care?
It's just a dog.
How's he doing, anyway?
He's got a couple hours left in him.
Long enough to help us get Einstein back.
And then we can shoot them both up and...
get their strength back for tomorrow.
So how come you guys couldn't get the effect to last longer, anyway?
I don't know, Zack. I was just a trainer.
I'm not a trainer.
Plan's back on, little brother.
Let's close up shop, huh?
Yeah.
Sure.
Let's go.
We're gonna do it.
Come on.
I'm gonna take the car.
All right.
I'll see you in a minute.
Yeah.
Thanks, man.
Bye-bye, Jack.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
I take it my son has proven to be a good hire.
Excellent.
He's taken a real passion for the project I've given him.
I gather this project does not require him to relocate out of Smallville?
Highly doubtful.
I underestimated you, Lex.
That's a common mistake.
But not one I usually make.
It seems that headstrong young men have become my blind spot.
First Jason, then now you.
You asked me to give Jason a position at Luther Corps.
I'm not sure I understand your problem.
You know exactly why I wanted you to hire Jason.
Get him away from Lana Lang.
But instead you decided to co-opt him for your own purposes.
Genevieve, paranoia is not a very attractive quality in a woman.
I'm just trying to protect my son.
Well, maybe you should get together with my father and write a parenting book.
I bet it'd be a bestseller.
Then you're no longer interested in how your father was released from prison.
I've chosen to believe my father truly is reformed.
Therefore, the question of his guilt or innocence no longer bothers me.
But it's great seeing you again, Genevieve.
And you too, Lex.
Give my best to Jason.
It's a shame he won't be able to help you find what you're looking for.
Go ahead and tell me his name, Your Honor...
How's ISub backup working?
Our fulfillment is still in effect.
Click on I am trying to give you additional support.
Do you want me to do a héctor partial and here's where I'm applying for a Chicago
National Service fields report?
The by Krabs, our temporary station.
I'm starting to believe he's as strong as Clark says he is.
Certainly is a beautiful dog.
Wait a minute, wait a minute. I know what you're thinking.
Well, it might be nice for Clark to have a dog.
It's been kind of a lonely year for him.
Well, wait a minute.
Then what happens when Clark goes off to college next year, huh?
Who winds up having to take care of that dog? Me.
Lois, it's time for dinner!
Hey, hey, hey!
You see?
Well, remember when Clark did that? He was only three.
It's not funny.
Hey!
What happened?
That's my T-bone.
Oh, bad dog.
I'm sorry.
Clark, grab a stick. I was just about to break.
Lex, is Luther Corp doing experiments on dogs?
I'm not really sure that's any of your business.
Lois found a stray dog. It has a Luther Corp ID tag.
Are you?
Clark, when I took over the company,
I found quite a few irregular experiments being conducted at my father's request.
One of them involved animal testing.
And the other one involved dog testing.
What were they doing?
If I remember correctly, they were mixing Meteor Rock with a steroid to enhance canine strength.
Why would your dad be interested in making super-powered dogs?
If I understood my father's insanity, Clark,
I'd be a much happier man.
I suppose in this case there were military applications.
I guess I'll never really know for sure.
The results were inconclusive.
I had animal rights activists picketing the site, so I closed it down.
I was told the dogs were destroyed.
Evidently not all of them.
Is it exhibiting any problems?
Is that your way of asking me if it has super strength?
I don't know.
I'm just trying to figure out what it is.
What are you trying to say?
You're telling me it's just a dog?
It's just a dog?
Is that your way of saying it's a dog?
No.
I assume you'd tell me that because I'd have quite a liability on my hands if he did.
The dog's perfectly healthy.
Well, then I'm sure the Kent farm will be a perfect home for him.
Sorry about dinner.
Guess it's just sandwiches tonight.
Jonathan?
Jonathan!
Stay back!
Martha!
Get away!
No!
Get away from him!
Get back!
Jonathan!
Sweetheart.
Mr. Kent.
Are you alright?
Yeah.
That's okay.
Lois, get the car keys.
We have to take him to the hospital.
Dad, what did they say?
Well, the doctor said he'd never seen a doctor.
He said he'd never seen a dog that could bite clean through bone before.
God, look at this.
The store owner's in a coma.
He was attacked by something that could pulverize a steel door.
And the police think it's a bear.
You think it was the dogs?
Someone's obviously controlling these dogs and using them.
Look, the only people that knew we had the dog were Lex and that guy at the animal shelter.
And since the boy billionaire probably doesn't go around robbing convenience stores...
We should check it out.
Well, let's do that first thing in the morning.
All right. Um...
Clark, would you give me a hand signing out, would you?
Look, son, I know that you're really attached to this dog,
but I'm worried it could be dangerous, even to you.
I know. That's why I have to find out who's doing this and stop them.
No, Clark.
Son, it won't make any difference.
If they had anything to do with putting that man in a coma,
then they're gonna have to be put down.
Dad, when you and Mom found a super-powered boy in a cornfield,
you didn't give up on me just because I might be dangerous.
You raised me. You gave me a chance.
He's a good dog, Dad.
Someone's just using him to do bad things.
We should give him a chance.
I want you to leave here with me tonight.
Why?
Because of Countess Margaret Isabel Thoreau?
You know that name, don't you?
Is this what Lex has you doing?
I don't know.
I don't know what Lex has you doing.
Researching 17th-century witches.
You're incapable of giving a straight answer, you know that?
So apparently, when Isabel was condemned to die,
she vowed to rise again through one of her descendants.
You knew that that was Lana, didn't you?
That's why you had me bring her to Isabel's tomb in Paris.
Because you knew that if she received the mark, then she was the one.
Which means it's... it's my fault that everything's happening to her.
You can't blame yourself.
How could you use me like that?
Look, it's not safe for you to stay here.
Well, I'm not leaving, Lana.
Perhaps you'll change your mind when you hear the rest of the story.
Isabel was condemned by a woman named Gertrude.
Isabel vowed that when she rose from the dead,
that she would wipe out all of Gertrude's heirs.
We're Gertrude's ancestors, Jason.
So you think that Lana's going to kill you?
No.
But Isabel will, and who knows when she'll return?
Mother, I walked out on Lana once before.
I'm not gonna do it again.
Then you're in love with a girl...
that may kill our entire family.
That is why I decided to oppose
What is this, an obstacle course?
You see him anywhere? Come here, Clarkie.
Come here, boy.
Wow.
Did the downer get any thicker in here?
You know, I've been thinking.
Clarkie might have had something to do with what happened at that convenience store,
but I don't think he hurt that guy.
There wasn't any blood on him when I found him.
We're not gonna call him Clarkie, okay?
We're gonna call him Bear, a bandit or something.
Uh, no and no.
What is all this?
It's Luther Court payroll.
They're gonna hit an armored truck.
It's happening right now.
Lois, call the police on this if I can catch up with these guys.
Hold on there, Forrest Gump.
What are you gonna do, run?
We brought my car, remember?
Lois, look.
We can call the cops on the way.
You are so weird sometimes.
Lois?
I'm sorry.
I know I shouldn't have asked you.
You know, can you go a little bit faster?
Hey, you weren't gonna be having it
about 10 minutes ago.
Besides, I don't wanna hit anything.
It should be right here.
Well, it's not.
Let's go.
Come on.
Just the money.
Grab the money.
Come on.
Okay?
Wait, turn left, turn left.
Why?
Here, just do it.
What is this, another one of your famous hunches
or are we just on a little scenic route here?
Okay, stop here.
What, where?
Here, stop here.
Okay.
Shut up, you dumb.
Grab the bags, let's go.
I am.
Come on, faster.
These guys back there don't look so good.
Forget about the guards.
Just the money, let's go.
All right, come on.
Come on.
Up the lock, little brother.
You gonna see if you can help those guards?
It's all right, buddy.
We'll get you out of here.
Come on.
What?
Take this.
We're going to get you out of here.
Don't move.
Oh, my God.
Take it easy.
Don't move.
Move.
What's he barking about?
I don't know.
But in five minutes, it won't matter.
We've been in the truck, the dogs, everything, all the evidence.
What?
We're going to be in the keys before anyone knows we're back here.
before anyone knows we're gone.
Where's Einstein?
What the hell?
It's that guy from the animal shelter.
Well, well, well.
Looks like someone has some explaining to do.
I don't know.
Well, you just had to be a hero, didn't you?
Sometimes heroes get burned.
Are you sure about this?
We saw their faces. We can't let them walk.
This wasn't part of the plan.
The plan's working, okay?
We got the money and we're almost out of here.
You're not gonna chicken out on me now, are you?
No.
I don't think so.
Come on.
You know all the bags have a truck, right?
Every time.
Come on.
You're not even talking.
You're not even eating.
You're not even slicing to eat.
Come on.
I'm sick of this.
Don't you find it.
Shut up, boy.
Make a wish, little brother.
Going somewhere?
I don't know.
This guy's quite a hero from what I understand.
Yeah, but my dad lets me keep him.
Doctor, you didn't notice anything unusual about any tests
you ran on him, did you?
Like what?
Well, he just seems really strong sometimes,
and he likes to get into things.
Well, if anything, I'd say his strength
is a little below average.
You got a perfectly normal, healthy dog there.
Have you thought of a name yet?
I was thinking of calling him Crypto.
Interesting name.
Well, I'd better be going.
Thanks, Dr. Klein.
You're welcome.
Crypto.
What's it mean?
Friendly.
It's because his background is so cryptic.
Speaking of his background, I went out
to the scene of the robbery and saw my armored truck.
From the look of the back doors, I
could only assume it was the handiwork
of some very strong dogs.
Lex, you told me I could keep him back when you thought
he was a failed experiment.
But Clark, if the experiment didn't fail,
this dog could be dangerous.
But he's not dangerous now.
He saved my life.
I'll take my chances on his loyalty.
Oh.
So do you mind telling me why I was up until 2 in the morning
researching Jason's family tree?
I mean, not that it wasn't, you know, halfway interesting.
It's just you definitely got your place
in the Guinness Book of Strange's last minute requests.
I saw him downstairs talking to his mom.
It was obviously a heated discussion.
But when he came up to the apartment, I said, hey, you know, I'm a little bit worried.
I was like, I don't know what to do.
I'm just a little bit worried.
I'm not a good boy.
I was a good boy.
He didn't even mention it to me.
Well, did you hear what they were talking about?
No.
But it clearly rattled him.
Chloe, he's keeping something from me.
You know, I don't even know who I can trust anymore.
Did you find anything?
Not much.
I mean, I could only go back as far as his mom's grandmother.
After that, it's like someone just chopped off a part of the family tree.
This is nothing.
there. I can tell you that she comes from a town called Castelnau du Mont Meral, but that's all I
know. Well, I accept that... Lana, are you okay? Chloe, this is the town that my ancestors come from
and Isabelle Thoreau. Well, on a scale of weird to ten, Genevieve's grandmother is the one who
moved Isabelle's tomb into that church in Paris. Why would anyone move a witch's tomb into a church?
I think that's something you need to ask Jason.
You're looking for my son. He's not here. I'm just returning something. Yes, yes. How's the
research coming?
I'm not sure I know what you mean. Yes, you do. I mean, Isabelle. I understand your hesitation. When I found out that you'd been hired by my son, I put a few of the pieces together and saw the connection. You, um, you're Genevieve Teague's boy?
Yes.
Of course.
You can't trust her, Jason. Of course, you can't trust my son either, but I think you know that.
I suppose you're gonna tell me I can trust you, though.
What's this?
Open it.
Here.
I think it might help you.
Here's the note.
Thank you.
Thanks.
I think it might help you.
Thank you.
Thanks.
I think it might help you.
Done.
Oh, it took you long enough.
Now you just have to fix the dining room table,
the window, the fence.
Ah!
Ugh.
I thought bathing was supposed to help with my allergies.
Well, maybe you're allergic to the soap, too.
Yeah, maybe I'm allergic to you.
Can you grab me a towel, please?
Thanks.
So, what are we gonna call him?
And don't give me any of the skipper crap.
I was thinking we'd call him Crypto.
Why? Because he's so cryptic, like you?
I don't think so.
Why not?
Because I think it's dumb.
You can call your next dog Crypto.
Look, it's not that hard.
Max, Lucky, Rocky, Bailey, Scamp,
they're all just like, you know,
Scamp, Naughty, Bud.
Hey, you're gonna have to pick one of those
if you wanna keep him.
Really?
You know, when I was a little girl,
we had a dog that looked just like this one.
Maybe that's why I liked him so much right away.
His name was Shelby.
I can live with that.
Well, it beats Clarkie.
Come on, Shelby.
Let's go, Sammy.
Come on, Will.